{
    "id": "a3cde080cc9d4cf5b045439cdceddd31",
    "title": "Join with a relative pronoun",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "828e08f0f6384b989962a8ab9b3c8f05",
            "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Our General Manager, .......................................... has retired, is planning to go abroad.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our child, ........................................... has no appetite for food, should be taken to the doctor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandmother, ............................................... can’t read or write, used to tell me a lot of stories.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This medicine, ........................................................ was prescribed by a native doctor, relieves pain instantly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what",
                        "who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My friend Charles, ................................................. was very dear to me, passed away last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met with an accident about ................................................... I shall tell you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to consult the doctor ................................................. treated me last year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whom",
                        "who",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our grandmother told us a story .................................................. we had not heard before.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "One of the boys ................................................... went on the study tour is missing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Students ................................................ belong to the Scheduled Castes and Tribes don’t have to pay the application fee.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}